<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on The Astro Wolfe</title>
    <link>https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on The Astro Wolfe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Certifications</title>
      <link>https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/certifications/</guid>
      <description>Conquering the exam. Credits   The IT industry has numerous ways to break into it and get ahead in your career. One of the quickest is through IT certifications. Whether you’re starting your career, expanding your expertise, or needing to comply with policies or mandates - certifications are the way to go! Many vendors offer certification, of which I highly recommend CompTIA due to being widely recognized and accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain Shopping Sprees</title>
      <link>https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/domain-buying-spree/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 22:50:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/domain-buying-spree/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a guilty pleasure of mine, but I LOVE buying domains. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember when or how it all started, but it&amp;rsquo;s more addictive than Pokémon - I GOTTA CLAIM &amp;lsquo;EM ALL! 😂
However, not everyone appreciates this perspective&amp;hellip; A while back, an article hit the front page of HackerNews describing how terrible domain parking is. I&amp;rsquo;m guilty of this, but I don&amp;rsquo;t regret it. From side projects to creative domains, it&amp;rsquo;s fun to grab a good URL and throw something up there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Made This Blog</title>
      <link>https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/how-i-made-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://theastrowolfe.com/blog/how-i-made-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>Warning: You are about to read a blog post on how this blog was made - It&#39;s getting meta.    Hugo: The world&amp;rsquo;s fastest framework for building websites. Credits   This blog is made with Hugo. &amp;ldquo;The world’s fastest framework for building websites.&amp;quot;1 Basically, it is a static site generator built in go. This means when it is time to build a website, it&amp;rsquo;s very fast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
